

CHEN, STEPHEN

MEDICAL STUDENT | WEBSITE: HTTPS://STEPHCLL.GITHUB.IO/CV/

SUMMARY

Medical Student who enjoys learning and has experience in computer science, finance, medicine, and teaching. I truly believe I can solve problems and help people by applying my expertise in research, communication, and teamwork to the tech industry.

SKILLS AND QUALIFICATIONS

- Google Analytics
- Google Project Management
- iOS Development
- HarvardX CS50
- Python
- HTML and CSS
- SQL
- Management tools Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint
- Trend Analysis
- Market Research
- Data organization
- Risk Management

EXPERIENCE

FINANCIAL PORTFOLIO MANAGEMENT • JANUARY 2016 - PRESENT

- Manage financial portfolios for a small number of close clients, including stocks, bonds, and budgeting.
- Research trends and company data and present data weekly
- Helped increase clients' savings by an average of 35% YOY

MEDICAL EXTERNSHIPS: VA CLINIC • ASSISTANT • AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT

- Develop and execute treatment plans with teams of doctors, to address patients' issues and concerns while minimizing risks
- Adapt to several hospital working environments on short notice
- Manage communication between patients and doctors

EDUCATION

PYTHON CERTIFICATE • AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT • APP BREWERY

Coding bootcamp for developing with Python

MEDICAL SCHOOL DPM • AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

Samuel Merritt University, CSPM; GPA: 3.62

B.S. BIOLOGY • AUGUST 2012 - JUNE 2016 • UC IRVINE

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- iOS multiple-choice app: Offline app for medical boards
 - Created a wireframe, wrote a database of questions, and collected feedback from other students.
- · Games: Snake, Pong, and trivia
 - o Created games using Python's Turtle class
- Lifestyle: Habit tracking, exercise tracking, and rain alert
 - Automatically stored data in CRT files and used Twilio API to send SMS alerts.
- Stock tracking program on Python
 - Alpha Vantage API to track movements in stock price and automatically send SMS with news when set price is hit.







